(Sheldon:)Hey, you taught me something.
(Sheldon:)Who would have thought it?
(Bernadette:)Okay.
(Penny:)Uh, no, the shipment
has not arrived,
(Penny:)and I really need those shoes.
(Penny:)They are my biggest seller.
(Penny:)Yes, ladies sizes six
through ten.
(Raj:)Thank you.
Oh, sorry.
(Penny:)I have to go.
I have a customer. Bye-bye.
(Penny:)Hi. Can I help you?
(Sheldon:)I'd like a frozen yogurt,
please.
(Penny:)Yogurt?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
Um...
(Penny:)Okay, sure.
(Penny:)Luckily, we sell both shoes
and yogurt here.
(Sheldon:)You do?
(Penny:)Yes. Look up at the sign,
(Penny:)and remember, improv is always
about saying yes.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)I see a sign.
It says "Camarillo State
Mental Hospital."
(Sheldon:)What?
(Sheldon:)It's the only explanation
I can come up with